#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/jon-michael-noblejas-421aa199 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Orthopedics
Operating Room
Robotic Surgery

# Jon Michael Noblejas

Registered Nurse - Operating Room Greater New York City Area

#### Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse Operating Room with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Surgical Oncology, Robotic Surgery, Ambulatory Surgery, Trauma Surgery, Orthopedics, ENT, and Ophthalmology. Strong healthcare services professional graduated from University of Santo Tomas.

### Experience

Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center Registered Nurse Operating Room-Oncology November 2016 - Present (3 years 9 months) Greater New York City Area

Kaiser Permanente
Registered Nurse Operating Room
March 2015 - June 2017 (2 years 4 months)
Tyson's Corner Virginia, and Gaithersburg, Maryland

Suburban Hospital OR Registered Nurse II April 2013 - March 2017 (4 years) Bethesda, Maryland

- -Responsible for independently planning, coordinating, and directing those activities essential to the provision of quality nursing care for assigned patients; coordinating the medical plan provided by support service departments relating to the assigned patients; identifying and implementing nursing interventions and evaluates results; and demonstrating developing leadership qualities.
- -- knowledgeable of the following surgeries: robotics, spine, general, neuro, peripheral vascular, urology, gyne, ortho

Alliant Healthcare Staffing
Operating Room Nurse - Traveler
September 2014 - November 2016 (2 years 3 months)
Washington D.C. Metro Area

Travel to assigned ambulatory surgery center. Responsible for independently planning, coordinating, and directing those activities essential to the provision of quality nursing care for assigned patients; coordinating the medical plan provided by support service departments relating to the assigned patients; identifying and implementing nursing interventions and evaluates results; and demonstrating developing leadership qualities.

HCR ManorCare RN Nurse Supervisor February 2012 - March 2013 (1 year 2 months) Homewood, Illinois

The RN-Nurse Supervisor supervises nursing personnel to deliver nursing care and within the scope of practice, coordinates care delivery which will ensure that residents' needs are met in accordance with professional standards of practice through physician orders, center policies and procedures, and federal, state and local guidelines. In return for your expertise, you'll enjoy excellent training, industry-leading benefits and unlimited opportunities to learn and grow. Be a part of the team leading the nation in healthcare.

Glenshire Nursing Home Charge Nurse/Staff Nurse January 2010 - July 2012 (2 years 7 months) Richton Park, Illinois

Responsible for managing RNs and CNAs for the residents' health plan and supervising the day-to-day resident care activities during the shift. Both care management and supervisory responsibilities must be executed in accordance with state and federal regulations and facility policies and procedures.

Makati Medical Center
Operating Room Nurse
September 2006 - September 2008 (2 years 1 month)
Makati City, Philippines

Responsible for the delivery of patient care through the utilization of the nursing process and based on the internationally accepted nursing practice standards. He/she is responsible for managing records, supplies and equipment; provide health education to patients and families and collaborates with other professional disciplines to ensure effective patient care delivery and the achievement of desired patient outcomes.

## Education

University of Santo Tomas BS Nursing · (1992 - 1996)

Ateneo de Manila University High school · (1980 - 1992)